Stop!
Parar!
Yiyu!
Sim!
Sinan!
Sinan!
It's my fault.
A culpa é minha.
I've caused you so much suffering.
Eu causei-lhe tanto sofrimento.
Nothing happened last night.
Não aconteceu nada ontem à noite.
I knocked Liu Silin unconscious
Deixei Liu Silin inconsciente
and managed to escape.
e conseguiu escapar.
This is...
Isto é...
This is the new servant at the Liu residence,
Este é o novo empregado da residência Liu,
Guo Zixin.
Guo Zixin.
This is the second young master of the Liu family,
Este é o segundo jovem mestre da família Liu,
Liu Sinan.
Liu Sinan.
How did you two end up together?
Como é que vocês os dois ficaram juntos?
To make a long story short,
Para encurtar a história,
I saved him.
Eu salvei-o.
I begged him to help me escape.
Implorei-lhe que me ajudasse a escapar.
Thank you, sir.
Obrigado, senhor.
No need.
Não há necessidade.
I pay my respects to you, Young Master.
Presto-lhe os meus respeitos, Jovem Mestre.
I've long heard that the Second Young Master is humble
Há muito tempo que ouço dizer que o Segundo Jovem Mestre é humilde
and compassionate.
e compassivo.
Now that I've met you,
Agora que te conheci,
I see the rumors are true.
Vejo que os rumores são verdadeiros.
You all flatter me too much.
Vocês bajulam-me todos demais.
We shouldn't stay here long.
Não devemos ficar aqui muito tempo.
We should leave quickly.
Devemos sair rapidamente.
Follow me.
Siga-me.
What are you doing?
O que estás a fazer?
Are you okay?
Está bem?
Let me take care of Yiyu.
Deixe-me cuidar do Yiyu.
Leave this place as soon as possible.
Deixe este lugar o mais rapidamente possível.
The farther you hide, the better.
Quanto mais se esconder, melhor.
So my brother won't catch you.
Para que o meu irmão não te apanhe.
He...
Ele...
He won't let you go.
Ele não o vai deixar ir.
Then I shall take my leave now.
Então vou despedir-me agora.
Thank you, Second Young Master and First Young Mistress, for saving my life.
Obrigado, Segundo Jovem Mestre e Primeira Jovem Mestra, por me terem salvo a vida.
Yiyu,
Sim,
are you all right?
está bem?
Let's go then.
Vamos então.
I haven't even asked you yet.
Eu ainda nem perguntei.
We were supposed to get married,
Nós deveríamos casar,
so why was I sent to the young master instead?
então porque fui enviado ao jovem mestre?
I swear,
Juro,
I knew absolutely nothing about this beforehand.
Eu não sabia absolutamente nada sobre isto antes.
Someone drugged me last night,
Alguém me drogou ontem à noite,
and by the time I woke up,
e quando acordei,
the wedding was already over.
o casamento já tinha terminado.
I... I swear,
Eu... juro,
if I'm lying even slightly,
se estiver a mentir, mesmo que um pouco,
may heaven strike me down.
que o céu me derrube.
Don't talk nonsense.
Não diga disparates.
I believe you.
Eu acredito em ti.
What should we do now?
O que devemos fazer agora?
I absolutely won't let you
Eu absolutamente não vou deixá-lo
go back to that awful place.
volte para aquele lugar horrível.
Whether it offends my father
Se isso ofende o meu pai
or means leaving this home,
ou significa deixar esta casa,
we must be together.
devemos ficar juntos.
Yiyu.
Possível.
Let's run away together.
Vamos fugir juntos.
But Sinan,
Mas Sinan,
I don't want you
Eu não te quero
to go against your entire family for me.
ir contra toda a sua família por mim.
It's not worth it.
Não vale a pena.
It is worth it.
Vale a pena.
For you,
Para ti,
anything is worth it.
qualquer coisa vale a pena.
Catch them!
Pegue-os!
Someone's coming!
Alguém está a chegar!
Let's go quickly!
Vamos depressa!
Stop right there!
Pare mesmo aí!
Don't run!
Não corra!
Father!
Pai!
Come back with me.
Volte comigo.
I won't.
Eu não vou.
You clearly know I love the Second Young Master.
Sabes claramente que eu amo o Segundo Jovem Mestre.
Why are you marrying me off to the First Young Master?
Porque é que me está a casar com o Primeiro Jovem Mestre?
Come here.
Vem cá.
The master had someone examine the First Young Master.
O mestre mandou alguém examinar o Primeiro Jovem Mestre.
They said the First Young Master
Disseram que o Primeiro Jovem Mestre
needs to marry a woman with compatible birth charts
precisa de casar com uma mulher com mapas astrais compatíveis
to bring good fortune.
para trazer boa sorte.
This way,
Por aqui,
the First Young Master's madness can be cured.
a loucura do Primeiro Jovem Mestre pode ser curada.
And you happen to be
E você acontece ser
that compatible woman.
aquela mulher compatível.
I remember Commander Xu's daughter
Lembro-me da filha do Comandante Xu
was previously engaged to the First Young Master.
foi anteriormente noiva do Primeiro Jovem Mestre.
Wasn't it because he went mad
Não foi porque enlouqueceu
that she broke off the engagement?
que ela rompeu o noivado?
I am your daughter.
Eu sou sua filha.
How could you do this to me?
Como é que me pôde fazer isto?
The master has been good to our family,
O mestre tem sido bom para a nossa família,
very good.
muito bom.
I'm also the master's confidant
Eu também sou o confidente do mestre
and the head steward of the Liu family.
e o mordomo-chefe da família Liu.
Is it because I'm your adopted daughter
É porque sou sua filha adoptiva
that you can sell me to the young master
que me pode vender ao jovem mestre
in exchange for your wealth and status?
em troca da sua riqueza e estatuto?
How dare you!
Como se atreve!
All these years I've treated you like my own daughter.
Todos estes anos tratei-a como se fosse minha filha.
You know that.
Você sabe disso.
Besides,
Para além de,
your birth father Jiang Huai and I
o seu pai biológico Jiang Huai e eu
were close friends for many years.
foram amigos próximos durante muitos anos.
When your parents were killed,
Quando os seus pais foram mortos,
I couldn't get there in time.
Não consegui chegar a tempo.
It's been weighing on my conscience for years.
Há anos que pesa na minha consciência.
I'm doing this for your own good.
Estou a fazê-lo para o seu próprio bem.
The young master is the legitimate son of the master.
O jovem mestre é o filho legítimo do mestre.
The master won't mistreat him in the future.
O mestre não o maltratará no futuro.
Besides, you've already been through the ceremony.
Além disso, já passou pela cerimónia.
It's too late to say anything now.
É tarde demais para dizer alguma coisa agora.
Come. Follow father home.
Venha. Siga o pai para casa.
I won't go back.
Não voltarei.
Uncle Qianfan.
Tio Qianfan.
Yiyu and I are in love.
O Yiyu e eu estamos apaixonados.
As for my father...
Quanto ao meu pai...
If someone's to blame,
Se alguém é o culpado,
blame me.
culpe-me.
No need to say more.
Não é preciso dizer mais nada.
Come back with me.
Volte comigo.
I beg you
eu te imploro
to let me be with Sinan.
para me deixar estar com o Sinan.
Take her away.
Leve-a embora.
Miss.
Faltar.
Father, I beg you to let us go.
Pai, peço-te que nos deixes partir.
You!
Tu!
What are you doing?
O que estás a fazer?
Put that knife down!
Baixe essa faca!
Don't come any closer.
Não se aproxime mais.
If you take one more step,
Se der mais um passo,
I'll kill myself right in front of you.
Vou matar-me bem na sua frente.
Fine.
Bom.
You may go.
Pode ir.
Sir,
Senhor,
I can't return empty-handed.
Não posso voltar de mãos a abanar.
I'll take responsibility for everything.
Assumo a responsabilidade por tudo.
Go.
Ir.
Thank you, Father, for your blessing.
Obrigado, Pai, pela tua bênção.
Yiyu.
Possível.
Let's go.
Vamos.
We'll stay here for tonight.
Ficaremos aqui esta noite.
Tomorrow morning I'll take you out of the city.
Amanhã de manhã levar-te-ei para fora da cidade.
Okay?
Ok?
Father.
Pai.
Mother.
Mãe.
Mother, wake up. Mother.
Mãe, acorde. Mãe.
Yiyu.
Possível.
What's wrong?
O que está errado?
Had another nightmare?
Teve outro pesadelo?
It's okay.
Está tudo bem.
Don't worry.
Não te preocupes.
I'm here for you.
Estou aqui para si.
Who are you people?
Quem são vocês?
What do you want?
O que queres?
Brother.
Irmão.
This is the only inn around here.
Esta é a única pousada por aqui.
Let's make do for one night.
Vamos contentar-nos com uma noite.
You dare to run away and elope with someone right under my nose.
Atreves-te a fugir e a casar com alguém mesmo debaixo do meu nariz.
You've got some nerve.
Tem muita coragem.
The fragrance pouch was found right here.
A bolsa de fragrâncias foi encontrada aqui.
You madman!
Seu louco!
I'd rather die than go with you.
Prefiro morrer a ir contigo.
Death
Morte
isn't that easy.
não é assim tão fácil.
In life, you belong to me,
Na vida, tu pertences-me,
in death, your ghost is mine.
na morte, o teu fantasma é meu.
Take the Second Young Master back,
Leve o Segundo Jovem Mestre de volta,
let my father deal with him.
deixe o meu pai lidar com ele.
Yes.
Sim.
Yu.
Você.
Cheng Wen Yi Li Bao Rong Wu
Cheng Wen Yi Li Bao Rong Wu
Wu Jinhua Hong Tao Rong Long Hong Xu Zhi
Wu Jinhua Hong Tao Rong Long Hong Xu Zhi
Chunguang Yandi
Chunguang Yandi
Kun Ji Ran Ping Xiang Shi Di Tao Lei Wen Li Bin Ping Cai Chao Lei Peng Chao Chang Ting Yue Bo Zhang Feng Chao Mei Zou Dong Zhu Qun Dong Liu Jing Hong Jun Lu
Kun Ji Ran Ping Xiang Shi Di Tao Lei Wen Li Bin Ping Cai Chao Lei Peng Chao Chang Ting Yue Bo Zhang Feng Chao Mei Zou Dong Zhu Qun Dong Liu Jing Hong Jun Lu
Lei Peng Chao Chang Ting
Lei Peng Chao Chang Ting
Yang Shi Di Tao Lei Wen Li Bin Ping Cai Chao Lei Peng Chao Chang Ting Yue Bo Zhang Feng Chao Nan Qin Dong Zhu Qun Dong Liu Jing Hong Jun Lu Ling Tuan Gang Hong
Yang Shi Di Tao Lei Wen Li Bin Ping Cai Chao Lei Peng Chao Chang Ting Yue Bo Zhang Feng Chao Nan Qin Dong Zhu Qun Dong Liu Jing Hong Jun Lu Ling Tuan Gang Hong
Wen Li Bin Ping Cai Chao Lei Peng Chao Chang Ting Yue Bo Zhang Feng Chao Nan Qin Dong Zhu Qun Dong Liu Jing Hong Jun Lu Ling Tuan Gang Hong Dong Bin You Ping Gang
Wen Li Bin Ping Cai Chao Lei Peng Chao Chang Ting Yue Bo Zhang Feng Chao Nan Qin Dong Zhu Qun Dong Liu Jing Hong Jun Lu Ling Tuan Gang Hong Dong Bin You Ping Gang
Ping Cai Chao Lei Peng Chao Chang Ting Yue Bo Zhang Feng Chao Nan Qin Dong Zhu Qun Dong Liu Jing Hong Jun Lu Ling Tuan Gang Hong Dong Bin You Ping Gang Qiu Liang Jun
Ping Cai Chao Lei Peng Chao Chang Ting Yue Bo Zhang Feng Chao Nan Qin Dong Zhu Qun Dong Liu Jing Hong Jun Lu Ling Tuan Gang Hong Dong Bin You Ping Gang Qiu Liang Jun
Chao Lei Peng Chao Chang Ting Yue Bo Zhang Feng Chao Nan Qin Dong Zhu Qun Dong Liu Jing Hong Jun Lu Ling Tuan Gang Hong Dong Bin You Ping Gang
Chao Lei Peng Chao Chang Ting Yue Bo Zhang Feng Chao Nan Qin Dong Zhu Qun Dong Liu Jing Hong Jun Lu Ling Tuan Gang Hong Dong Bin You Ping Gang
Feng Chao Nan Qin Dong Zhu Qun Dong Liu Jing Hong Jun Lu Ling Tuan Gang Hong Dong Bin You Ping Gang Qiu Liang Jun Han Fa Shan Kai Yue Qiu Wei Shuo Heng Wei Gang
Feng Chao Nan Qin Dong Zhu Qun Dong Liu Jing Hong Jun Lu Ling Tuan Gang Hong Dong Bin You Ping Gang Qiu Liang Jun Han Fa Shan Kai Yue Qiu Wei Shuo Heng Wei Gang
Zhu Qun Dong Liu Jing Hong Jun Lu Ling Tuan Gang Hong Dong Bin You Ping Gang Qiu Liang Jun Qian Fa Shan Kai Yue Qiu Wei Shuo Heng Wei Gang Feng Xia Dong Guan Long
Zhu Qun Dong Liu Jing Hong Jun Lu Ling Tuan Gang Hong Dong Bin You Ping Gang Qiu Liang Jun Qian Fa Shan Kai Yue Qiu Wei Shuo Heng Wei Gang Feng Xia Dong Guan Long
Jing Hong Jun Lu Ling Tuan Gang Hong Dong Bin You Ping Gang Qiu Liang Jun Qian Fa Shan Kai Yue Qiu Wei Shuo Heng Wei Gang Feng Xia Dong Guan Long Zong Lin Sheng Mian
Jing Hong Jun Lu Ling Tuan Gang Hong Dong Bin You Ping Gang Qiu Liang Jun Qian Fa Shan Kai Yue Qiu Wei Shuo Heng Wei Gang Feng Xia Dong Guan Long Zong Lin Sheng Mian
Hong Dong Bin You Ping Gang Qiu Liang Jun Qian Fa Shan Kai Yue Qiu Wei Shuo Heng Wei Gang Feng Xia Dong Guan Long Wan Lin Sheng Meng Xin Lu Long Gang Chun Ni Tian
Hong Dong Bin You Ping Gang Qiu Liang Jun Qian Fa Shan Kai Yue Qiu Wei Shuo Heng Wei Gang Feng Xia Dong Guan Long Wan Lin Sheng Meng Xin Lu Long Gang Chun Ni Tian
Ping Gang Qiu Liang Jun Qian Fa Shan Kai Yue Qiu Wei Shuo Heng Wei Gang Feng Xia Dong Guan Long Wan Lin Sheng Tian Xin Lu Long Gang Chun Ni Tian Ying Jing Long Xue
Ping Gang Qiu Liang Jun Qian Fa Shan Kai Yue Qiu Wei Shuo Heng Wei Gang Feng Xia Dong Guan Long Wan Lin Sheng Tian Xin Lu Long Gang Chun Ni Tian Ying Jing Long Xue
Liang Jun Qian Fa Shan Kai Yue Qiu Wei Shuo Heng Wei Gang Feng Xia Dong Guan Long Wan Lin Sheng Meng Xin Lu Long Gang Chun Ni Tian Ying Jing Long Xue Jing Jun Fei Chao
Liang Jun Qian Fa Shan Kai Yue Qiu Wei Shuo Heng Wei Gang Feng Xia Dong Guan Long Wan Lin Sheng Meng Xin Lu Long Gang Chun Ni Tian Ying Jing Long Xue Jing Jun Fei Chao
Kai Yue Qiu Wei Shuo Heng Wei Gang Feng Xia Dong Guan Long Wan Lin Sheng Meng Xin Lu Long Gang Chun Ni Tian Ying Jing Long Xue Jing Jun Fei Chao Hui Dong Le Yan
Kai Yue Qiu Wei Shuo Heng Wei Gang Feng Xia Dong Guan Long Wan Lin Sheng Meng Xin Lu Long Gang Chun Ni Tian Ying Jing Long Xue Jing Jun Fei Chao Hui Dong Le Yan
Yue Qiu Wei Shuo Heng Wei Gang Feng Xia Dong Guan Long Wan Lin Sheng Meng Xin Lu Long Gang Chun Ni Tian Ying Jing Long Xue Jing Jun Fei Chao Hui Dong Le Yan Han
Yue Qiu Wei Shuo Heng Wei Gang Feng Xia Dong Guan Long Wan Lin Sheng Meng Xin Lu Long Gang Chun Ni Tian Ying Jing Long Xue Jing Jun Fei Chao Hui Dong Le Yan Han
Wei Gang Feng Xia Dong Guan Long Wan Lin Sheng Meng Xin Lu Long Gang Chun Ni Tian Ying Jing Long Xue Jing Jun Fei Chao Hui Dong Le Yan Han Rui Long Tuo
Wei Gang Feng Xia Dong Guan Long Wan Lin Sheng Meng Xin Lu Long Gang Chun Ni Tian Ying Jing Long Xue Jing Jun Fei Chao Hui Dong Le Yan Han Rui Long Tuo
Dong Guan Long Wan Lin Sheng Meng Xin Lu Long Gang Chun Ni Tian Ying Jing Long Xue Jing Jun Fei Chao Hui Dong Le Yan Han Rui Long Tuo Bo
Dong Guan Long Wan Lin Sheng Meng Xin Lu Long Gang Chun Ni Tian Ying Jing Long Xue Jing Jun Fei Chao Hui Dong Le Yan Han Rui Long Tuo Bo